<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DH.J</title>
    <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DH.J</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.dhjeong.kr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to HKMC Gen5W Firmware Decryption?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2024/02/hkmc-firmware-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2024/02/hkmc-firmware-tools/</guid>
      <description>Overview Last year, a tool was released that allowed users to extract HKMC(Hyundai KIA Motors Group) Gen5W firmware.&#xA;hkmcavn-tools (@galaxy4public)&#xA;This tool is made to work with the firmware of Head Unit products designed by LGE.&#xA;Available Target (AU) 2022-23 Sportage&#xA;(AU) 2021-23 IONIQ5&#xA;&amp;hellip;&#xA;Download Navigation Updater Download the33333 Navigation Updater from Hyundai Motors Group below link. Download Navigation Updater [Figure 1] Download Navigation updater Settings for Navigation Updater By selecting the Hyundai or KIA brand from the main screen and entering a non-member login, you can view the settings screen below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Ubertooth BR/EDR Sniff</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2024/02/ubertooth-bt-sniff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2024/02/ubertooth-bt-sniff/</guid>
      <description>Overview I recently tried sniffing bluetooth packets via ubertooth.&#xA;As far as we know, ubertooth has provided sniffing capabilities for Bluetooth low energy (BLE), but in a recent update, firmware was developed to allow sniffing of Bluetooth packets for the Bluetooth Classic (BR/EDR) specification.&#xA;This is included in the release firmware (2020-12-R1), but it is not the default application, so you can build your own firmware and use the and flash it to your ubertooth device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fuzzing USB stack in real cars</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/12/how-to-fuzzing-realcar-defcon31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/12/how-to-fuzzing-realcar-defcon31/</guid>
      <description>Overview PoC for vulnerability in real cars vehicle infotainment system&#xA;The research was presented at the DEFCON31 Car Hacking Village, you can watch additional footage at the link below!&#xA;Video: DEFCON31_CarHackingVillage_Automotive-USB-Fuzzing&#xA;Description This research could lead to a crash of the vehicle infotainment system via USB in produced vehicles.&#xA;It has been tested on some produced vehicles, but we believe it can be tested on any vehicle that supports USB input and could have an impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My talks and CTF Participation at DEFCON31 Car Hacking Village</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/08/ctf-talks-defcon31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/08/ctf-talks-defcon31/</guid>
      <description>CTF On the 10th, I participated in the Car Hacking Village CTF at the DEFCON hacking conference in Las Vegas as a member of Autocrypt, which consisted of a total of 13 people. We secured a commendable 4th place finish in the competition. Special thanks to @uberwoozle for organizing this event.&#xA;[Figure 1] CHV31 CTF Final Scoreboard Talks On 10 August I gave a presentation on &amp;lsquo;Automotive USB Fuzzing&amp;rsquo; at the Car Hacking Village at DEFCON in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23082 Vulnerability Reporting and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/05/cve-2023-23082/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/05/cve-2023-23082/</guid>
      <description>Overview A few months ago I started doing vulnerability analysis research on open source projects and this is a quick review of vulnerabilities for one of them, the Kodi project by the XBMC Foundation.&#xA;The vulnerability was categorized as a heap overflow and a DOS vulnerability and assigned CVE-2023-23082.&#xA;More information can be found at cve.mitre.org.&#xA;CVE-2023-23082&#xA;Analysis The vulnerability occurs in the logic of parsing image files in the Kodi process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awarded a bounty of $500 for BMW Automotive</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/03/bmw-bugbounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2023/03/bmw-bugbounty/</guid>
      <description>Overview In recent months, we previously conducted a vehicle vulnerability analysis for BMW Automotive. This vulnerability is a service crash vulnerability, which could result in a potential denial of service.&#xA;[Figure 1] BMW Automotive Awarded a bounty of 500$ [Figure 2] BMW GROUP HALL OF FAME </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTF Participation at DEFCON30 Car Hacking Village</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2022/08/ctf-defcon30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/2022/08/ctf-defcon30/</guid>
      <description>Overview On the 12th, I participated in the Car Hacking Village CTF at the DEFCON hacking conference in Las Vegas as a member of Autocrypt, which consisted of a total of 7 people. We secured a commendable 5th place finish in the competition. Special thanks to @uberwoozle for organizing this event.&#xA;The competition featured several automotive-related hacking challenges, including car simulators, analysing vehicle firmware, obtaining ECU information, and Bluetooth hacking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/about/</guid>
      <description>Bio Name. DONGHYEON JEONG Contact. dhje0ng(at)naver.com Experience &amp;#x1f3e2; Autocrypt Redteam (2021.06 ~ Now)&#xA;Vehicle Penetration Testing, Threat Analysis (and) Risk Assessment (ISO/SAE 21434) &amp;#x1f468;&amp;zwj;&amp;#x1f468;&amp;zwj;&amp;#x1f467;&amp;zwj;&amp;#x1f466; DEMON TEAM/POC Security (2020.08 ~ Now)&#xA;Vulnerability Research Security Traning (Middle/High/University Students) CTF(Capture the Flag) Contest Operation &amp;amp; Participation Skill Language C/C++ Python .JS (Node) Java Docker Hacking Web Hacking Embedded Hacking Hardware Chip Identity/Analysis/Extracting Firmware Analysis Reverse Engineering Cloud AWS (EC2, S3 Bucket, DB &amp;hellip;) Cooperation Git, Confluence, Teams, Slack Education Yeungnam University Collage (2018.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
