<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DH.J</title>
    <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DH.J</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Ubertooth BR/EDR Sniff</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/2024/02/ubertooth-sniff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/2024/02/ubertooth-sniff/</guid>
      <description>Summary I recently tried sniffing bluetooth packets via ubertooth.&#xA;As far as we know, ubertooth has provided sniffing capabilities for Bluetooth low energy (BLE), but in a recent update, firmware was developed to allow sniffing of Bluetooth packets for the Bluetooth Classic (BR/EDR) specification.&#xA;This is included in the release firmware (2020-12-R1), but it is not the default application, so you can build your own firmware and use the and flash it to your ubertooth device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fuzzing USB stack in real cars</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/12/how-to-fuzzing-realcars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/12/how-to-fuzzing-realcars/</guid>
      <description>Overview PoC for vulnerability in real cars vehicle infotainment system&#xA;The research was presented at the DEFCON31 Car Hacking Village, you can watch additional footage at the link below!&#xA;Video: DEFCON31_CarHackingVillage_Automotive-USB-Fuzzing&#xA;Description This research could lead to a crash of the vehicle infotainment system via USB in produced vehicles.&#xA;It has been tested on some produced vehicles, but we believe it can be tested on any vehicle that supports USB input and could have an impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BH CTF - Write up</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/ctf/2023/11/blockharbor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:10:10 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/ctf/2023/11/blockharbor/</guid>
      <description>Summary Blockharbor CTF Season 1&#xA;https://ctf.blockharbor.io&#xA;dhjisgod (9th)&#xA;[Figure 1] BHCTF ScoreBoard Challenges TBD (coming soon) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My talks at DEFCON31 Car Hacking Village</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/11/chv-dc31-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/11/chv-dc31-talks/</guid>
      <description>Summary On 10 August I gave a presentation on &amp;lsquo;Automotive USB Fuzzing&amp;rsquo; at the Car Hacking Village at DEFCON in Las Vegas.&#xA;The above topic is a presentation that describes the process of discovering USB vulnerabilities in real-world vehicles, including the CVE-2022-39075 and CVE-2022-39076 vulnerabilities, and how to effectively perform USB fuzzing in the vehicles we studied.&#xA;See the following links for more information!&#xA;DEFCON31-Automotive_USB_Fuzzing_RealWorld</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Hacking Village at DEFCON31</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/08/chvctf-dc31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/08/chvctf-dc31/</guid>
      <description>Summary On the 10th, I participated in the Car Hacking Village CTF at the DEFCON hacking conference in Las Vegas as a member of Autocrypt, which consisted of a total of 13 people. We secured a commendable 4th place finish in the competition. Special thanks to @uberwoozle for organizing this event.&#xA;We also had a presentation at this year&amp;rsquo;s Car Hacking Village on &amp;ldquo;AUTOMOTIVE USB FUZZING: HOW TO FUZZING USB IN VEHICLES TO DISCOVER THE REAL-WORLD VULNERABILITIES&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review a CVE-2023-23082</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202305/cve-2023-23082/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202305/cve-2023-23082/</guid>
      <description>Overview A few months ago I started doing vulnerability analysis research on open source projects and this is a quick review of vulnerabilities for one of them, the Kodi project by the XBMC Foundation.&#xA;The vulnerability was categorized as a heap overflow and a DOS vulnerability and assigned CVE-2023-23082.&#xA;More information can be found at cve.mitre.org.&#xA;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-23082 Vulnerability The vulnerability occurs in the logic of parsing image files in the Kodi process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awarded a bounty of $500 for BMW Automotive</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202303/bmw_automotive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202303/bmw_automotive/</guid>
      <description>Summary In recent months, we previously conducted a vehicle vulnerability analysis for BMW Automotive. This vulnerability is a service crash vulnerability, which could result in a potential denial of service.&#xA;[Figure 1] BMW Automotive Awarded a bounty of 500$ [Figure 2] BMW GROUP HALL OF FAME </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGL (Automotive Grade Linux) Platform</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2022/12/agl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2022/12/agl/</guid>
      <description>Summary [사진 1] AGL Overview AGL (Automotive Grade Linux) OS란?&#xA;https://www.automotivelinux.org/about/members/&#xA;전 세계 차량 OEM 들과 협력하에 개발되고 있는 인포테인먼트 시스템이다.&#xA;AGL은 IVI(In Vehicle Infortainment) 시장을 목표로 하고 있다.&#xA;AGL 개발 자체는 오픈소스 프로젝트로 진행되며 AGL 이외에도 대표적으로 GENIVI 라는&#xA;플랫폼도 존재하는데 두 회사 모두 IVI S/W 개발 환경을 제공하여 다른 차량 OEM 회사들이&#xA;IVI 시스템을 쉽게 개발할 수 있도록 하는 목적을 가진다.&#xA;[사진 2] AGL/GENIVI Overview [사진 3] AGL Core AGL OS 에 올라가는 코어 부분의 구성도이다.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2022 POWER OF XX 예/본선 대회 운영기</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/202211/poxx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 11:36:24 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/202211/poxx/</guid>
      <description>Summary 지난 10월 8일 그리고 이틀 전인 11월 10일 두 번에 걸쳐서 2022 POWER OF XX 대회를 운영하였다.&#xA;예/본선 모두 CTF 플랫폼과 문제 인스턴스 등 인프라 전체 관리를 맡았고 약간의 문제(?)를 제외하면 성공적으로 대회를 운영한 것 같다.&#xA;이번에 운영했을 때 인프라를 어떻게 구성했는지를 간단하게 썰로 풀어보려고 한다.&#xA;Server Instance Name Description Spec Main-Server CTFd(v3.5.0) c5.2xlarge(8CPU, 16RAM, SSD 8GIB) Challenge-Server Ubuntu 22.04 AMD64 c5.4xlarge(16CPU, 32RAM, SSD 32GIB) 우선 서버 인스턴스는 총 2개로 메인 서버 - 문제 서버를 생성해서 사용하였다.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Instrument Cluster Simulator</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2022/10/icsim_simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 11:36:24 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2022/10/icsim_simulator/</guid>
      <description>Summary 최근 자동차 해킹에 대한 소재가 많이 떠오르고 있다. 때문에 자동차 보안에 대해서도 관심을&#xA;가지시는 분들이 많을 것 같다고 생각을 하고 있다.&#xA;이번 글에서는 자동차에 들어가는 주요 통신 프로토콜 중 하나인 CAN 프로토콜이 어떤건지, 그리고&#xA;자동차의 계기판을 시뮬레이터로 만들어둔 도구를 하나 소개할 것이다.&#xA;(이 도구를 통해서 CAN 통신이 어떻게 이루어지는지를 간단하게 공부해볼 수 있다)&#xA;CAN Protocol Controller Area Network 의 약자로,&#xA;차량 내에서 Host PC 없이 Controller 또는 Device간 통신을 주고 받기 위해 사용하는 자동차 표준 통신 규격이다.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON 30th Car Hacking Village 참가 후기 SSUL</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/202210/defcon30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 16:36:20 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/202210/defcon30/</guid>
      <description>Summary 코시국으로 인해 세계 최대 해킹 컨퍼런스인 데프콘(DEFCON) 행사도 몇 년간 온라인으로 진행이 됐었다.&#xA;그!러!나 22년도에는 드디어 오프라인으로 데프콘 행사가 열리게 된다는 소식을 접할 수 있었다.&#xA;마침 우리 회사 팀장님이 DEFCON MAIN TALK 이랑 Car Hacking Village 에 CFP 를 제출했던 것이 Aceept 되셔서&#xA;데프콘 행사에 참가할 수 있는 명분이 생겼다. (학회 참가 &amp;amp; 대회 참가 등..)&#xA;그래서 갔다. Las Vegas 를 향해서&#xA;라스베이거스 현지 스트립 거리 도착!&#xA;끼니는 뭘 먹었을까?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VirtualBox Remote Code Execution Study</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/2022/01/vbox-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/2022/01/vbox-escape/</guid>
      <description>Summary A study of known vulnerabilities against VirtualBox (virtualization software) in 2022 that led to a Remote Code Execution (RCE) attack.&#xA;Although this is a known vulnerability, there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been much published about the details of the specifics of the analysis process,&#xA;so I thought this might be helpful to someone in the future.&#xA;Open the Link - Notion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 사이버보안챌린지 자동차 해킹&amp;방어 대회 우승 후기</title>
      <link>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/202112/csc2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/notes/202112/csc2021/</guid>
      <description>Summary 이번 하반기에 진행된 사이버보안챌린지 2021 차량 해킹&amp;amp;방어 대회에서,&#xA;회사 소속으로 출전해서 최우수상 을 수상하게 되었다!&#xA;대회 환경이 AGL (Automotive Grade Linux) 라고 하는 차량 인포테인먼트 시스템 이미지를 주고,&#xA;그 시스템 안에서 취약점을 분석하고 찾아서 공격하는 것이 공격(예선전) 이였다.&#xA;처음엔 막연하게 Low 단까지 접근해서 라이브러리 취약점도 분석하고&#xA;각 서비스들 Daemon 분석하면서 취약점을 찾았었는데 원하는 결과가 잘 나오지 않았다.&#xA;실제로 라이브러리 RCE 취약점이 존재했지만 해당 시스템 상에서 트리거가 안되서 무용지물 이였다.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
