<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>carhacking on DH.J</title>
    <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/tags/carhacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in carhacking on DH.J</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blog.dhjeong.kr/tags/carhacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My talks at DEFCON31 Car Hacking Village</title>
      <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/11/chv-dc31-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/11/chv-dc31-talks/</guid>
      <description>Summary On 10 August I gave a presentation on &amp;lsquo;Automotive USB Fuzzing&amp;rsquo; at the Car Hacking Village at DEFCON in Las Vegas.
The above topic is a presentation that describes the process of discovering USB vulnerabilities in real-world vehicles, including the CVE-2022-39075 and CVE-2022-39076 vulnerabilities, and how to effectively perform USB fuzzing in the vehicles we studied.
See the following links for more information!
DEFCON31-Automotive_USB_Fuzzing_RealWorld</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Hacking Village at DEFCON31</title>
      <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/08/chvctf-dc31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/automotive/2023/08/chvctf-dc31/</guid>
      <description>Summary On the 10th, I participated in the Car Hacking Village CTF at the DEFCON hacking conference in Las Vegas as a member of Autocrypt, which consisted of a total of 13 people. We secured a commendable 4th place finish in the competition. Special thanks to @uberwoozle for organizing this event.
We also had a presentation at this year&amp;rsquo;s Car Hacking Village on &amp;ldquo;AUTOMOTIVE USB FUZZING: HOW TO FUZZING USB IN VEHICLES TO DISCOVER THE REAL-WORLD VULNERABILITIES&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM Equinox Automotive Infotainment Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202307/gm-chevrolet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202307/gm-chevrolet/</guid>
      <description>CVE-2023-39076 PoC for vulnerability in General Motors Automotive Infortainment System
Summary This is a proof of concept for CVE-2023-39076, which allows a USB attack on the infotainment system in General Motors vehicles. This could allow an attacker to crash the infotainment system.
Affected GM Chevrolet Equinox 2021 (at version, 2021.03.26 build ver) DEMO Copyright Donghyeon Jeong / dhje0ng(at)naver.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renault ZOE Automotive Infotainment Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202307/renault-zoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202307/renault-zoe/</guid>
      <description>CVE-2023-39075 PoC for vulnerability in Renault Automotive Infortainment System
Summary This is a proof of concept for CVE-2023-39075, which allows a USB attack on the infotainment system in Renault vehicles. This could allow an attacker to crash the infotainment system.
Affected Renault ZOE EV 2021 (at versions, 283C35202R ~ 283C35519R) DEMO Copyright Donghyeon Jeong / dhje0ng(at)naver.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen Jetta Automotive Infotainment Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202307/volkswagen-jetta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202307/volkswagen-jetta/</guid>
      <description>Information Vehicle model : Volkswagen Jetta 2021
Hardware version : 724
Software version : 0876
Summary We analyzed the vulnerabilities in the infotainment system of Volkswagen Jetta vehicle and found a USB memory vulnerability that caused the infotainment to crash.
Analysis TBD (No plans to go public yet.)
Impact This attack could allow an attacker to abnormally shut down the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s infotainment system (resulting in an internal crash).
DEMO Copyright Donghyeon Jeong / dhje0ng(at)naver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awarded a bounty of $500 for BMW Automotive</title>
      <link>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202303/bmw_automotive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.dhjeong.kr/posts/vuln/202303/bmw_automotive/</guid>
      <description>Summary In recent months, we previously conducted a vehicle vulnerability analysis for BMW Automotive. This vulnerability is a service crash vulnerability, which could result in a potential denial of service.
[Figure 1] BMW Automotive Awarded a bounty of 500$ [Figure 2] BMW GROUP HALL OF FAME </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
